

# ARKADIUSZ KOWALCZYK

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

### CONTACT

695-096-965

arekkowalczyk47@gmail.com

github.com/dev-arson github.com/arsonDev



Opoczno, Poland

#### SKILLS

- React Native
- Metro
- Android
- Android TV
- React.JS
- iOS (basics)
- GIT
- Jenkins
- Altassian (Jira, Confluence)
- Playstore
- Firebase
- Kotlin
- Java
- JavaScript
- TypeScript

#### REFERENCES

#### Mped Sp.z.o.o

"I have been working with Arek for 15 months. During this time, he showed understanding of the client's needs and perfect adaptation to the changing conditions of cooperation.

Hiring him was a great decision, thanks to highly developed communication skills I am convinced that he will do great in any team."

#### EDUCATION

#### **Engineer**

#### Lodz University of Technology

Computer science - software engineering 2015-2021

### LANGUAGES

English **B2** 

Polish Native

#### ACTIVITIES

- Charity stock App React Native Pomodoro App React Native Step counter Android

- App for freelancer developers Web & API
- Stock application for online store Android
- ToDoList Desktop ToDoList Android

### PROFILE

I am 28 years old passionate of computer technology especially in mobile development. I try to resolve problem I encounter with high accuracy and professionalism. I like to learn generally, although in context of more technical stuff. My passion is develop apps in React Native and Android native but I like to try something new e.g Artificial Intelligence or IoT

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Software Engineer**

Redge Technologies

- Developed and maintained React Native apps for iOS and Android platforms in JavaScript and TypeScript
- Developed and maintained Android TV apps in Kotlin
- Developed and maintained Android Libraries for other apps related with video playback in Kotlin
- Provided technical leadership by mentoring junior engineers on best practices related to software development and engineering processes
- Implementation of new technologies to projects and introduced build variants based features
- Provided technical interviews for React Native and Android Native devs
- Released and maintained apps in Google Play Store, Firebase, AppStore Connect

- Go3 (LV,LT,ES) (Android, Android TV) Redge Media Portal (Mobile)
- Tv3Play (Android, Android TV)
- FreeTV (Mobile)
- VOD.PL (Mobile)
- Redge Media Player (Android)
- Misot Group (Mobile, Android TV)
- FlixClassic
- EntClick

# **Fullstack Engineer**

Mped Sp. z.o.o

Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2022

Dec. 2021 - Current

- Developed and maintained React.JS web applications in JavaScript
- Developed and maintained .NET Core/ .NET Framework applications in C#
- · Maintained MS SQL database with integrations via .NET Core
- Provided APIs endpoints to web applications
- Analyzed clients needs and prepare technical descriptions of task to do

#### **Projects**

- · Internal AXA Projects
- HeatDecor.pl

# **Software Engineer**

Speedmail Sp. z.o.o

May. 2019 - Aug. 2020

- Created and maintained Android application with integration with existing
- Developed and maintained Desktop application in .NET
- · Maintained MS SQL database and improved existing solutions to provide high performance application
- Create analysis and custom raports providing possibility solution to decide in wide term

#### Projects

- Internal Speedmail integration system
- · Mobile application for postman's

### Software Engineer / Technical Support

Azako Sp. z.o.o

Mar 2016 - Apr 2019

- Created and maintained Desktop application with integration with existing systems
- Developed and maintained Desktop application in .NET
- Provided technical support of hardware and software